Create a virtual machine instance running Docker container

Usage:
  yc compute instance create-with-container <INSTANCE-NAME> [Flags...] [Global Flags...]

Flags:
      --name string                                                     
                A name of the instance.
      --description string                                              
                Specifies a textual description of the instance.
      --labels key=value[,key=value...]                                 
                A list of label KEY=VALUE pairs to add.
      --zone string                                                     
                The zone of the instance to create.
      --metadata key=value[,key=value...]                               
                Metadata to be made available to the guest operating system running on the instance.
                See for details https://cloud.yandex.ru/docs/compute/concepts/vm-metadata
      --metadata-from-file key=value[,key=value...]                     
                Same as --metadata except that the value for the entry will be read from a local file.
      --ssh-key string                                                  
                Creates user 'yc-user' and adds SSH key from specified file to authorized keys using cloud-config.
                If your need more flexibility, use cloud-config passed in 'user-data' metadata key.
      --public-ip                                                       
                If true, one-to-one NAT public IP will be created for the default network interface. Cannot be passed together with --network-interface
      --public-address string                                           
                If set, one-to-one NAT public IP will be created for the default network interface with the specified value. Cannot be passed together with --network-interface
      --create-disk PROPERTY=VALUE[,PROPERTY=VALUE...]                  
                Creates and attaches persistent disks to the instance.
                
                Possible property names:
                
                name
                   Specifies the name of the disk.
                
                type
                   The type of the disk. To get a list of available disk types, run 'yc compute disk-type list'. The default disk type is network-hdd.
                
                size
                   The size of the disk in GB. You can also use M and T suffixes to specify smaller or greater size respectively. If not specified, inferred size is used. If the disk is created from a snapshot, disk size of the snapshot is used. If the disk is created from an image, size of the image is used.If no source is specified, default disk size is used.
                
                block-size
                   Specifies the block size of the disk in bytes. You can also use K and M suffixes.
                
                snapshot-name
                   A source snapshot used to create the disk.
                
                snapshot-id
                   An ID of the source snapshot used to create the disk.
                
                image-name
                   A source image used to create the disk.
                
                image-id
                   An ID of the source image used to create the disk.
                
                image-family
                   An image family that is used to create the disk.
                
                image-folder-id
                   The folder ID that is used to resolve references for image-name or image-family.
                
                disk-placement-group-id
                   An ID of the placement group to create the disk in
                
                disk-placement-group-name
                   A placement group to create the disk in
                
                device-name
                   Specifies a unique serial number of your choice that is reflected into the /dev/disk/by-id/ tree of a Linux operating system running within the instance.
                
                auto-delete
                   Specifies if this persistent disk will be automatically deleted when the instance is deleted.
                
                
      --attach-disk PROPERTY=VALUE[,PROPERTY=VALUE...]                  
                Attaches persistent disks to the instances. The specified disks must already exist.
                
                Possible property names:
                
                disk-name
                   The disk to attach to the instance.
                
                disk-id
                   An ID of the disk to attach to the instance.
                
                device-name
                   Specifies a unique serial number of your choice that is reflected into the /dev/disk/by-id/ tree of a Linux operating system running within the instance.
                
                auto-delete
                   Specifies if this persistent disk will be automatically deleted when the instance is deleted.
                
                
      --create-boot-disk PROPERTY=VALUE[,PROPERTY=VALUE...]             
                Creates a new disk and uses it as a boot disk of the instance.
                
                Possible property names:
                
                name
                   Specifies the name of the disk.
                
                type
                   The type of the disk. To get a list of available disk types, run 'yc compute disk-type list'. The default disk type is network-hdd.
                
                size
                   The size of the disk. If not specified, inferred size is used. If the disk is created from a snapshot, disk size of the snapshot is used. If the disk is created from an image, size of the image is used.If no source is specified, default disk size is used.
                
                device-name
                   Specifies a unique serial number of your choice that is reflected into the /dev/disk/by-id/ tree of a Linux operating system running within the instance.
                
                auto-delete
                   Specifies if this persistent disk will be automatically deleted when the instance is deleted.
                
                
      --use-boot-disk PROPERTY=VALUE[,PROPERTY=VALUE...]                
                Uses an already existing disk as a boot disk of the instance.
                
                Possible property names:
                
                disk-name
                   The disk to attach to the instance.
                
                disk-id
                   An ID of the disk to attach to the instance.
                
                device-name
                   Specifies a unique serial number of your choice that is reflected into the /dev/disk/by-id/ tree of a Linux operating system running within the instance.
                
                auto-delete
                   Specifies if this persistent disk will be automatically deleted when the instance is deleted.
                
                
      --attach-filesystem PROPERTY=VALUE[,PROPERTY=VALUE...]            
                Attaches filesystems to the instances. The specified filesystems must already exist.
                
                Possible property names:
                
                device-name
                   This value can be used to reference the device for mounting, resizing, and so on, from within the instance.
                
                filesystem-name
                   The filesystem to attach to the instance.
                
                filesystem-id
                   An ID of the filesystem to attach to the instance.
                
                
      --attach-local-disk PROPERTY=VALUE[,PROPERTY=VALUE...]            
                Attaches local disks to the instances.
                
                Possible property names:
                
                size
                   The size of the local disk in bytes. You can also use M and T suffixes to specify MiB or TiB respectively.
                
                
      --network-settings PROPERTY=VALUE[,PROPERTY=VALUE...]             
                Network settings for the instance.
                
                Possible property names:
                
                type
                   Type of a network for virtual machine instance. Values: standard, software-accelerated
                
                
      --network-interface PROPERTY=VALUE[,PROPERTY=VALUE...]            
                Adds a network interface to the instance.
                
                Possible property names:
                
                subnet-name
                   Specifies the subnet that the interface will be part of.
                
                subnet-id
                   Specifies the ID of the subnet that the interface will be part of.
                
                address
                   Assigns the given internal address to the instance that is created. If no address is specified, some unassigned address from the subnet is used.
                
                ipv4-address
                   Assigns the given internal IPv4 address to the instance that is created. If 'auto' used as value, some unassigned address from the subnet is used.
                
                nat-ip-version
                   Specifies IP version for One-to-One NAT. Can be 'ipv4'. This flag can be applied to network interfaces with ipv4 address.
                
                nat-address
                   Specifies public IP address for One-to-One NAT. This flag can be applied to network interfaces with ipv4 address.
                
                security-group-ids
                   Security groups for the network interface, security-group-ids=[id1,id2],security-group-ids=id3
                
                dns-record-spec
                   DNS records in format {name=<name>[,ttl=<ttl>][,dns-zone-id=<id>][,ptr={true|false}]}
                
                
      --memory byteSize                                                 
                Specifies how much memory instance should have.
      --cores int                                                       
                Specifies how many CPU cores instance should have.
      --core-fraction int                                               
                If provided, specifies baseline performance for a core in percent.
      --gpus int                                                        
                Specifies how many GPUs instance should have.
      --platform string                                                 
                Specifies platform for the instance.
      --hostname string                                                 
                Creates instance with specified hostname.
      --preemptible                                                     
                Creates preemptible instance.
      --placement-group-id string                                       
                Placement group to create the instance in.
      --placement-group-name string                                     
                Placement group to create the instance in.
      --host-group-id string                                            
                Host group to create the instance in.
      --host-group-name string                                          
                Host group to create the instance in.
      --host-id string                                                  
                Host to create the instance in.
      --service-account-id string                                       
                Service account, which token can be obtained inside VM from metadata service.
      --service-account-name string                                     
                Service account, which token can be obtained inside VM from metadata service.
      --async                                                           
                Display information about the operation in progress, without waiting for the operation to complete.
      --container-arg value[,value]                                     
                A list of arguments to append to container entrypoint. Overrides default container CMD
      --container-command string                                        
                Executable to run when the container starts. Overrides default container ENTRYPOINT
      --container-env key=value[,key=value...]                          
                Declare environment variable KEY with value VALUE passed to container. Only the last value of KEY is taken when KEY is repeated more than once.
                Values, declared with --container-env flag override those with the same KEY from file, provided in --container-env-file.
      --container-env-file string                                       
                Declare environment variables in a file. Values, declared with --container-env flag override those with the same KEY from file.
                File must contain lines in format KEY=VALUE, variables without value are not supported.
      --container-image string                                          
                Container image name.
      --container-name string                                           
                Container name.
      --container-privileged                                            
                Specify whether to run container in privileged mode.
      --container-stdin                                                 
                Open container STDIN.
      --container-tty                                                   
                Allocate a pseudo-TTY for the container.
      --container-restart-policy string                                 
                Specify whether to restart a container on exit. Must be one of: Always, Never, OnFailure. Default: Always.
      --container-volume-tmpfs PROPERTY=VALUE[,PROPERTY=VALUE...]       
                Add tmpfs-backed docker volume
                
                Possible property names:
                
                name
                   Specifies the name of the volume. (required)
                
                mount-path
                   Specifies the mount path of the volume inside a container. (required)
                
                
      --container-volume-host-path PROPERTY=VALUE[,PROPERTY=VALUE...]   
                Add docker volume bound to host path
                
                Possible property names:
                
                name
                   Specifies the name of the volume. (required)
                
                mount-path
                   Specifies the mount path of the volume inside a container. (required)
                
                ro
                   Specifies whether the volume is read-only or not inside a container. Default: false
                
                host-path
                   Specifies a path on host VM that will be bound to the volume. (required)
                
                
      --docker-compose-file string                                      
                Docker compose file.
      --coi-spec-file string                                            
                Container optimized image YAML file.

Global Flags:
      --profile string       Set the custom configuration file.
      --debug                Debug logging.
      --debug-grpc           Debug gRPC logging. Very verbose, used for debugging connection problems.
      --no-user-output       Disable printing user intended output to stderr.
      --retry int            Enable gRPC retries. By default, retries are enabled with maximum 5 attempts.
                             Pass 0 to disable retries. Pass any negative value for infinite retries.
                             Even infinite retries are capped with 2 minutes timeout.
      --cloud-id string      Set the ID of the cloud to use.
      --folder-id string     Set the ID of the folder to use.
      --folder-name string   Set the name of the folder to use (will be resolved to id).
      --token string         Set the OAuth token to use.
      --format string        Set the output format: text (default), yaml, json, json-rest.
  -h, --help                 Display help for the command.
